alphaindustries.com 2017-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Alpha Industries

**1\. Our Commitment**

 **Transparency** \- We tell you in advance what information we collect from you and how we intend to use it and how long we keep it. We may amend this policy from time to time so it is your responsibility to review the policy. By using our web site and providing any information, you are agreeing to be bound by our privacy policy. 

**Choice** \- We will not share your Personally Identifiable Information or other sensitive information you give us with third parties unless we first obtain your consent. We also will give you the opportunity of opting out of other uses that we make of any of the information you provide to us. If we change our Privacy Policy in any material way we will obtain your consent before changing the way we use your Personally Identifiable Information.

 **Security** \- We will implement reasonable security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology and other tools to protect all the information we collect about you on our websites. We will retain your Personally Identifiable Information only for the time necessary to achieve the disclosed purposes.

**2\. What Information Do We Collect? How Do We Collect It?**   
We collect two types of information on our websites: 

_Personally Identifiable Information ("PII")_  
Any information that can be used to identify you, such as your name, address, e-mail, or phone number. PII also includes your browsing history if that has been linked to your email address. _Anonymous Information (“Non-PII”)_  
All Information other than PII. For example, the fact that your browser has visited a particular page at a website is Anonymous Information because it does not identify you by name, address, or email. 

We collect PII and/or Non-PII depending on the purpose and functionality of each website (www.alphaindustries.com & www.shopalphaindustries.com) 

_How Do We Collect Information?_   
We collect Personally Identifiable Information when you register for promotional emails, set up a shopping account, contact customer service, and place an order through www.alphaindustries.com. Such Personally Identifiable Information may also be collected through our partners and vendors who work with us to provide our customers with enhanced services. To the extent these third party entities have their own privacy policies and terms of use, such privacy policies and terms of use shall also govern how your information is used. It is your responsibility to review all applicable third party privacy policies and terms of use before providing any such information to these entities. 

We collect Anonymous Information through the use of "cookies" and "web beacons." Cookies and web beacons work together to collect and process information regarding how your computer interacts with our Alpha Industries, Inc. (www.alphaindustries.com & www.shopalphaindustries.com) websites.

In addition, we may also at times use pixel tags, which allow us to read and use cookies. This permits us to gather certain information such as the time when a user has visited our site, IP addresses, and the type of browser being used. This process permits us to help customize your experience with our web site, including provision of information that may be of interest to you, e.g., advertisements.

 _What is a cookie?_  
A "cookie" is a computer file that acts as an identification card for your computer. The purpose of the cookie is to distinguish your browser from all other browsers that visit our websites. By recognizing your browser, we can serve you better. For example, the cookies allow us to hold the selections in your shopping cart when you navigate away from the order page and then return to complete the order; because of the cookie, you don't have to start over with your shopping. We can also keep track of what pages of our website your browser visited and whether you purchased a product. For some purposes, it may be necessary for you to permit us to use cookies. Disabling cookies may affect your use of our web sites.

**3\. Why We Collect Your Information**   
There are three important reasons why we collect information on our websites.   
• First, we collect Personally Identifiable Information to open your online shopping account, to complete online purchases, to answer your customer service questions and occasionally, to send to you (with your permission after you register online) information and email promotions about our products, and.  
• Second, we collect Anonymous Information that helps us keep track of information for the purposes of improving our website, improving our services and advertising, and measuring the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns.  
• Third, we collect Anonymous Information to provide you tailored advertising that we believe you will be much more interested in than randomly-generated advertisements.

 _Disclosure and Sharing of Information:_  
We will not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your PII to outside parties without providing you with advance notice and an opportunity to consent. "Outside parties" do not include companies wholly-owned by Alpha Industries, Inc. or our affiliates or authorized distributors or licensees. We reserve the right to disclose your PII and any non-PII at any time to the extent we reasonably believe that disclosure is required by law, to enforce our website policies, or to protect your or others' rights, property or safety. 

**4\. Your Choices Regarding Your Information**

 _PII / Promotional Emails:_  
There are several ways in which you can tell us whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. You may contact us through email, fax, or our customer support line. You also will have an opportunity to opt-out of promotional email by clicking on an "unsubscribe" link contained in promotional emails we send you. If you have any difficulty managing your communication preferences, please contact our Customer Service Department by email [CustomerService@alphaindustries.com](mailto:customerservice@alphaindustries.com). _Non-PII / Tailored Advertisements:_  
Most browsers accept cookies automatically. We recommend that you leave cookies "turned on" so that we can offer you a better shopping experience on our e-commerce website found at http://www.alphaindustries.com. However, you can easily disable your cookies. For example, if you use Windows, you can disable cookies from Microsoft Explorer by clicking on "Tools," "Internet options" and adjusting your settings under the "Security" tab. For more information and assistance disabling cookies on your browser, check out http://www.aboutcookies.org 

**5\. Links to Other Websites**   
Alpha Industries, Inc. websites may contain "hyper-links" to other third party websites. We recommend that you check the specific privacy policy of any site before providing any PII or allowing non-PII to be collected. We do not control these third party web sites and all use of such web sites are at your own risk.

**6\. We Do Not Collect Children's Information**  
Alpha Industries, Inc. websites are not intended to be directed towards individuals under 13 years of age ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect any PII from Children and our web sites are not intended to be used by Children. 

**7\. International Users**  
If you are visiting www.alphaindustries.com or www.shopalphaindustries.com from a location outside of the U.S., your connection will be through and to servers located in the U.S., your orders placed through www.alphaindustries.com or www.shopalphaindustries.com will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from the U.S. and all information you provide will be processed and maintained in our Web servers and internal systems located within the U.S. 

**8\. Contact Us Regarding Your Information**  
If you have any questions or concerns about Alpha Industries, Inc. Online Privacy Policy, please contact us through any of the following mediums:  
Email [CustomerService@AlphaIndustries.com](mailto:customerservice@AlphaIndustries.com)  
Toll-Free 1-866-631-0719   
Fax (U.S.) 1-703-378-4910 

Corporate Headquarters:  
Alpha Industries, Inc.   
14200 Park Meadow Drive   
Suite 110 South Tower   
Chantilly, VA 20151 USA 

Please be assured that any Personally Identifiable Information that you provide in communications to the above email, telephone number and postal address will not be used to send you promotional materials. If you contact us through email, fax, or phone we may collect your name, email address, mailing address and any information that you provide. 

**9\. Online Updates to the Privacy Policy**  
If we modify this Privacy Policy, we will post the revised Privacy Policy on this website. We also may post a notice on this website or send an email describing the changes. You should check this website regularly to see if any recent changes to this Privacy Policy have occurred. We will not make any change to this Privacy Policy that will change our collection and use of your PII without first obtaining your consent. 

**10\. Your Consent**  
By providing personal information to us through our website or through our customer service department in connection with our website, you're agreeing to let us collect and use your personal information as we describe in this Privacy Policy. 

This online Privacy Policy was last updated on October 6, 2014.
